shewearsmanyhats.com 2019-06-29

# Privacy | She Wears Many Hats

**She Wears Many Hats Privacy Policy**

 **Your privacy is important.  
**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy this notice is provided explaining the online information practices here at SheWearsManyHats.com and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, it’s made available on the homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. By visiting SheWearsManyHats.com you are consenting to this privacy policy. This policy may be updated periodically. It is your responsibility to review this policy from time to time to be aware of any updates and changes.

She Wears Many Hats found at <https://shewearsmanyhats.com/> is governed by the following privacy policy.

We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you what personally identifiable information we may collect and how it may be used. This statement only applies to this website.

WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT AND HOW IS IT USED?

 **Information You Voluntarily Submit to this website** : We may collect personal information from you such as your name or email address. For example, you may voluntarily submit information to this website by leaving a comment, subscribing to a newsletter, or submitting a contact form. In addition, you are able to create a user profile, which allows you to create a username and password. We will store the username, but your password will not be visible in our records.

 **Information We Collect from Others** : We may receive information about you from other sources. You may link your Facebook, Instagram, and/or Google accounts to your user profile.  If you choose to link your Facebook, Instagram, and/or Google accounts to your user profile, we will receive your name, email address and profile picture associated with that account.  This website utilizes the Facebook commenting system, so if you choose to comment on a website post, your profile picture will appear.

 **Automatically-Collected Information** : We automatically collect certain information about you and the device with which you access this website. For example, when you use this website, we will log your IP address, operating system type, browser type, referring website, pages you viewed, and the dates/times when you accessed this website. We may also collect information about actions you take when using this website, such as links clicked.

 **Cookies** : We may log information using cookies, which are small data files stored on your browser by this website. We may use both session cookies, which expire when you close your browser, and persistent cookies, which stay on your browser until deleted, to provide you with a more personalized experience on this website.

HOW YOUR INFORMATION MAY BE USED

We may use the information collected in the following ways:

  * To operate and maintain this website;
  * To create your account, identify you as a user of this website, and customize this website for your account; 
  * To send you promotional information, such as newsletters. Each email promotion will provide information on how to opt-out of future mailings;
  * To send you administrative communications, such as administrative emails, confirmation emails, technical notices, updates on policies, or security alerts;
  * To respond to your comments or inquiries;
  * To provide you with user support;
  * To track and measure advertising on this website;
  * To protect, investigate, and deter against unauthorized or illegal activity.

THIRD-PARTY USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We may share your information with third parties when you explicitly authorize us to share your information.

Additionally, this website may use third-party service providers to service various aspects of this website. Each third-party service provider’s use of your personal information is dictated by their respective privacy policies.

This website currently uses the following third-party service providers:

Google Analytics – this service tracks this website’s usage and provides information such as referring websites and user actions on this website. Google Analytics may capture your IP address, but no other personal information is captured by Google Analytics.

Mail Chimp – this service is used for delivery of email updates and newsletters. We store your name and email address for purposes of delivering such communications.  Please refer to [Mail Chimp’s privacy policy](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/) for further information.

One Signal – this service is used to send you push notifications through your web browser, should you choose.  Please refer to [One Signal’s privacy policy](https://onesignal.com/privacy_policy) for further information.

At this time, your personal information is not shared with any other third-party applications. This list may be amended from time to time in this website’s sole discretion.

Except when required by law, we will not sell, distribute, or reveal your email addresses or other personal information without your consent; however, we may disclose or transfer personal information collected through this website to third parties who acquire all or a portion of our business, which may be the result of a merger, consolidation, or purchase of all or a portion of our assets, or in connection with any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding brought by or against us.

ANONYMOUS DATA

From time to time, we may use anonymous data, which does not identify you alone, or when combined with data from other parties. This type of anonymous data may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Examples of this anonymous data may include analytics or information collected from cookies.

PUBLICLY VISIBLE INFORMATION

If you create a user profile on this website or leave a comment, certain information may be publicly visible.  To create a user profile, you must choose a username and password and input your email address for profile confirmation. Your email address will never be available publicly. At your option, you may also add an avatar, a profile description, and a link to your website.

You may also choose to link your Facebook, Instagram, and Google Account.

Users may see your username, avatar, profile description and website information.

COOKIES

This website uses cookies to store visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, customize website content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends. Cookies may also be used by third-party services, such as Google Analytics, as described herein.

Users may, at any time, prevent the setting of cookies, by this website, by using a corresponding setting of your internet browser and may thus permanently deny the setting of cookies. Furthermore, already set cookies may be deleted at any time via an Internet browser or other software programs. This is possible in all popular Internet browsers. However, if users deactivate the setting of cookies in your Internet browser, not all functions of our website may be entirely usable.

ADVERTISING

 **Display Ads**

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve content and advertisements when you visit this website, which may use cookies, as noted above. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices to opt-in or opt-out of this data collection, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

 **Retargeting  Ads**

From time to time, this website may engage in marketing efforts with third-party companies, such as Google, Facebook, Pinterest, or Instagram, in order to market this website. These companies use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to this website.

Facebook: Opt-out of Facebook remarketing [here](https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217)

Google: Opt-out of Google remarketing [here](https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217)

 **Affiliate Program Participation**

This website may engage in affiliate marketing, which is done by embedding tracking links into this website. If you click on a link for an affiliate partnership, a cookie will be placed on your browser to track any sales for purposes of commissions.

She Wears Many Hats is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and links to Amazon.com.  As part of this Amazon Associates program, this website may post customized links, provided by Amazon, to track the referrals to their website. This program utilizes cookies to track visits for the purposes of assigning commission on these sales.

Newsletters

On this website, you may subscribe to our newsletter, which may be used for advertising purposes. All newsletters sent may contain tracking pixels. The pixel is embedded in emails and allows an analysis of the success of online marketing campaigns. Because of these tracking pixels, we may see if and when you open an email and which links within the email you click. Also, this allows this website to adapt the content of future newsletters to the interests of the user. This behavior will not be passed on to third parties.

RIGHTS RELATED TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Opt-out – You may opt-out of future email communications by following the unsubscribe links in our emails. You may also notify us at amy@shewearsmanyhats.com to be removed from our mailing list.

Access – You may access the personal information we have about you by submitting a request to amy@shewearsmanyhats.com.

Amend – You may contact us at amy@shewearsmanyhats.com to amend or update your personal information.

Forget – In certain situations, you may request that we erase or forget your personal data. To do so, please submit a request to amy@shewearsmanyhats.com.

Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes or to complete transactions, or when required by law.

SENSITIVE PERSONAL INFORMATION

At no time should you submit sensitive personal information to this website. This includes your social security number, information regarding race or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious beliefs, health information, criminal background, or trade union memberships. If you elect to submit such information to us, it will be subject to this privacy policy.

CHILDREN’S INFORMATION

This website does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 16. If a parent or guardian believes that this website has personally identifiable information of a child under the age of 16 in its database, please contact us immediately at amy@shewearsmanyhats.com and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

CONTACT INFORMATION

At any time, please contact us at amy@shewearsmanyhats.com for questions related to this privacy policy.
